Honey, you're back.
老公 你回來啦
Do you want to take a shower,
你要先洗澡
have your dinner,
先吃飯
or have me instead?
還是先吃我
I'm going to devour you whole right now.
我想馬上把妳吃掉
Naughty Satou, you're so pervy.
討厭啦 佐藤你好色
What?
怎麼會
"HUH?" Hold on...
奇怪
Nephrites, let's begin.
涅芙麗緹絲 我要做囉
Yes, Lord Satou.
好 佐藤陛下
Wait! I'm supposed to be lying there!
等等 那是我的位置
No!
不要
Oh my, that was just a dream.
搞什麼 原來是夢啊
Here you go.
來
It's hot, don't burn yourself.
很燙 小心點喔
Yes.
好
Hime, you're finally awake.
小姬 妳醒啦
Dinner is ready.
晚餐做好了喔
Yeah.
嗯
Get as much rest as possible.
能休息的時候就儘量休息
Which kingdom should we head to now?
我們接下來要去哪個戒之國呢
The Kingdom of Water,
我打算去水之國
the dragonkin's nation.
那是龍人族的國家
Great.
好提議
I've always wanted to visit that place.
我也一直很想去看看
Ouch!
好燙
Are you all right?
妳沒事吧
It's still too hot.
好像還很燙
Come to think about it,
這麼說起來
Satou has been spending
佐藤他最近
a lot of time with Nephrites.
一直陪在涅芙麗緹絲身邊
Satou, where is mine?
佐藤 我的份呢
Sorry, Hime. You can help yourself with it.
抱歉 妳自己去盛吧
Wh...
什…
People normally wouldn't go that far!
一般人會做到這種地步嗎
Hime?
小姬
Forget what I said!
當我沒說
What is that sound?
這是什麼聲音
What is this thing?
這是什麼
A moving city?
街道在移動
Today is our lucky day.
真幸運
I never expected to see it here.
沒想到會在這種地方遇到
Behold, the Kingdom of Fire, Needakitta.
這就是火之國尼妲齊達
This is the giant moving city of the catfolk knights.
是貓人族到處遷徙的騎士國度
TALES OF WEDDING RINGS
《婚戒物語》
It's actually a country?
這是國家
I was wondering where to find them.
我本來還在煩惱要去哪裡找他們
We can't miss this opportunity.
不能錯過這個良機
Let's go to the princess and get the Ring of Fire.
先去找這裡的公主拿火之戒吧
We can head for the Kingdom of Water afterwards.
晚點再去水之國
I see.
這樣啊
Why is he so eager to go to the Kingdom of Water?
他那麼想去水之國嗎
Does he have closed ones there?
是不是有熟人在那裡呢
How do we get inside?
不過我們要怎麼進去這東西裡
Leave that to me.
包在我身上
Hey there! Can we get in there?
喂 可以讓我們上去嗎
A ladder?
梯子
Time to go up.
快爬上去吧
The air is too dusty.
不然到處都塵土飛楊
"SHAKING" Nephrites!
(站不穩) 涅芙麗緹絲
I think this is where I bid you farewell.
我要在此跟大家告別了
It's been a fun journey.
這趟旅程很愉快
She suddenly gave up!
突然就放棄了
Get it together, Nephrites!
沒事的 涅芙麗緹絲
I will...
我會…
Satou!
佐藤
"HOLDING TIGHTLY" I can take care of Nephrites!
(抱緊) 我會負責照顧涅芙麗緹絲
Okay.
好
Keep it up.
加油
Hyah!
嘿咻
Hey! What are you staring at?
喂 你在看哪裡啊
Hey! Be careful!
危險
Please be careful.
小心點
It'd be game over if you fell.
掉下去的話可是會完蛋的
Nephrites.
涅芙麗緹絲
You've done well.
妳真努力
I'm exhausted.
我已經筋疲力盡了
This is the order of knights?
這就是騎士團
It looks like a market street in every aspect.
但是不管怎麼看 都像是一條商店街
Needakitta consists of the Order of Knights of Fire,
尼妲齊達是身強體壯的貓人族
which consists of the strong catfolks.
組成的火之騎士團
Merchants will travel with them to seek protection.
旅行的商人為了尋求庇護 與他們的一起行動的過程中
Before they knew it, it's become a massive caravan.
不知不覺就形成龐大的商隊
It's just the same as the books!
跟書上寫的一模一樣
You are very knowledgeable.
妳真了解呢
It's said the catfolks lost their land in the earliest era of the Ring King.
據說貓人族在最早的戒王時代 失去國土後
They ended up building a city on moving platforms,
就在車上建立都城
slowly becoming a travelling tribe that offered armed services.
變成周遊列國販賣武藝的民族
Perhaps it's more befitting to call them mercenaries.
傭兵團這個稱呼也許更容易理解
But the strongest order of knights
不過世界最強的騎士團
has become the safest travelling caravan.
現在已經變成 世界最安全的移動市場了
The Kingdom of Fire brings merchandise from different countries
火之國尼妲齊達所到之處
wherever they end up going.
都能為所有城市 帶來各式各樣的商品
All right,
好了
let's ask them to take us to the Ring Princess of Fire.
先去拜託他們 讓我們見見火戒公主吧
Huh? The two are gone.
奇怪 她們倆不見了
Incredible!
好厲害
Simply incredible!
太厲害了
A trove of rare books!
有好多稀有的書
These are Imma'unia from the Memorandum of Dusk!
這是薄暮備忘錄裡記載的 伊瑪烏尼亞伊
Lord Satou, look at these!
佐藤陛下 你看看
This is...
這個…
Huh?
奇怪
I think we got separated.
我們好像走散了
Is it a bad thing?
是不是不太妙
NOISES
(吵雜)
What... What do we do now?
怎…怎麼辦
There are strangers everywhere!
到處都是不認識的人
Ewww... I feel sick.
噁 好想吐
Sorry.
對不起
I kept causing you more trouble.
我一直給妳添麻煩
It's all right. I don't mind that.
沒關係啦 別在意
Hey, are they the catfolks?
我問妳 那就是貓人嗎
Yes. Their looks fit the descriptions from my books.
沒錯 長得跟書上寫的相同
They are so cute with those cat ears.
好可愛 就像貓耳一樣
Not cute at all!
一點也不可愛
The ancient warrior blood flows in their veins.
他們身上流著古代戰士的血脈
They are a tribe of savages that served the Ring King with violence.
是用暴力和蠻橫 替戒王效力的野蠻民族
That's what the book says.
書上是這麼寫的
Besides, the elves' ears are cuter.
而且精靈的耳朵比較可愛
See how long they are?
長長的
Well...
這…這樣啊
You two over there.
妳們兩個
Are you lost?
該不會是迷路了吧
Yes.
對
We got separated from our friends.
我們和朋友走散了
I see.
這樣啊
When you are lost in Needakitta,
要是在尼妲齊達迷路了
simply walk towards the arena.
就往競技場的方向走
It's the most conspicuous landmark around.
那裡是最醒目的地標
Thank... Thank you so much!
謝…謝謝妳們
I hope you find your friends.
祝妳們與朋友順利會合
They are different from the books.
跟我在書上看到的好像不同
Where did you go, Hime
妳們跑到哪去了 小姬
and Nephrites?
涅芙麗緹絲
Calm down, Satou.
冷靜點 佐藤
Needakitta is a very safe place.
尼妲齊達的治安很好
There is only one place we should be,
我們該去的地方只有一個
which is where the Ring Princess of Fire is.
那就是火之公主的所在地
I'm so worried...
我好擔心
Everyone has been staring at us.
別人一直盯著我們看
Are you sure we are safe here?
這裡真的沒問題嗎
The catfolks have great respect for the strong.
那是因為貓人族最尊敬強者
I see.
原來如此
It's the imposing aura I'm giving off.
是我散發出了強大的氣場嗎
Sorry, but I am already in love.
不好意思 我已經心有所屬
Hi there!
那個
Judging by your poise and figure,
看您的站姿和身材
you must be a famous swordsman!
應該是位有名的劍士
Would you like to join us for some tea?
方便的話 能不能跟我們喝杯茶
Don't judge a book by its cover.
不能光憑外表判斷
The man over there is much stronger than me.
那邊的男性要比我強多了
Oh my, I like your sense of humour.
討厭 您真會開玩笑
"OUCH" That's hurtful.
打擊
He barely has any muscles on him.
那個人根本沒有半點肌肉嘛
By the way,
對了 請問一下
we are here to have an audience with the princess.
我們是來見這個國家的公主
Do you know where she is?
妳們知道去哪裡可以見到她嗎
Another one of her admirers?
又是來追公主的嗎
I get it.
我懂了
You must have come here to have a blind date with her.
你們也是來跟公主相親的吧
A blind date?
相親?
This must be the arena.
這裡就是競技場吧
Here you go.
來
Thank you.
謝謝
This is loaded with Imma'unia.
放了好多伊瑪烏尼亞伊
This looks so yummy.
看起來好好吃
I find it a bit gross.
我倒是覺得有點可怕
This tastes heavenly.
好好吃
A lot sweeter than I thought.
沒想到還滿甜的
You got a smudge on your face.
妳的嘴邊沾到了喔
Come on.
真是的
Princess Krystal, you act just like Lord Satou.
克莉絲朵殿下和佐藤陛下一模一樣
How so?
哪裡一樣了
You are both very kind.
非常體貼這一點
Travelling with you
跟你們兩位在一起
reminds me of having my parents' protection.
就像被爸爸和媽媽守護一樣
"DAD, MUM, DAUGHTER" I'm like a mother to you?
(爸爸 媽媽 女兒?) 媽媽…
Hold on, you're much older than me!
不對 妳比我們大耶
It's too weird for me to have a daughter like you!
當女兒也太勉強了吧
It's nothing.
沒什麼
I've always wanted to apologise to you.
我一直想向妳道歉
What for?
為什麼
Lord Satou has been taking care of me so attentively lately.
因為我最近老是受到 佐藤陛下的照顧
I don't mind at all!
那種事我一點也不在意
Unlike me, you're a delicate princess who's been safeguarded for so long.
跟我不同 妳是備受呵護的公主
Besides, Satou likes caring for people.
而且佐藤本來就喜歡照顧人
But that still makes you jealous.
可是妳會嫉妒吧
Well... You're right about that.
那倒是沒錯
You only feel this way because you love him.
因為妳很愛他才會覺得心痛
It's evident how deep your love for Lord Satou goes.
我認為這是妳真心 愛著佐藤陛下的證明
I, on the other hand,
相較之下
can only look at him with admiration.
我只是用憧憬的眼光看著他
My feelings for him aren't as strong as yours.
還無法擁有像妳那麼強烈的情感
Is someone like me
我這個樣子
even capable of fulfilling my duty as the Ring King's wife?
真的有辦法 完成身為戒王妻子的使命嗎
Unbelievable.
真是的
This guy never stood a chance.
這傢伙也完全不是對手啊
Satou?
佐藤
Hime!
小姬
Nephrites is with you too.
涅芙麗緹絲也跟妳在一起嗎
Something is not right.
情況有點不妙
We just saw a man get beaten.
剛才有個男人被揍得好慘
Why?
為什麼啊
Come now!
來吧 就是這裡
Come for a blind date with Her Highness!
公主的相親會場
This is the princess of Needakitta?
她就是火之國的公主
Who is next?
下一個相親對象是誰
Are you the Ring King?
你是戒王嗎
To become my husband,
想當我的丈夫
you must be stronger than me.
就必須比我強
Are you strong?
你夠強嗎
We'll know soon.
我來試試
Satou!
佐藤
What a disappointment.
真不像樣
I was quite excited when I heard you were the chosen Ring King.
聽說你是被選為戒王的人 我本來還很期待
Can a weak man with those rings
弱小的人得到戒指
really defeat Abyssal Creatures?
真的有辦法打贏深淵的魔物嗎
If you want a rematch,
要是想跟我再戰
come again.
那就改天再來吧
There are plenty of people waiting to have a blind date with me.
因為想跟我相親的人多得是
Observe your opponent's eyes.
要仔細盯著對手的眼睛
If you focus too much on the sword's movements...
光是在意劍的動向
This happens.
就會這樣
Ouch.
好痛
I couldn't even land a hit.
連碰都碰不到
Not even once.
完全不行
Come now, comrades of the Ring King.
來 戒王和同行的夥伴
It's time to get your food.
吃飯時間到了
All right. Let's take a break.
好了 稍微休息一下吧
Only a strong warrior can hope
想成為火之公主的丈夫
to marry the Ring Princess of Fire.
就必須是個強者
But we're in a predicament
不過傷腦筋的是
where no one in this country can beat her.
國內沒有任何男性能贏過公主
Therefore, we invited men from various races around the world
因此我們決定徵求全世界的種族
to have a blind date with her.
來當公主的相親對象
Granart Needakitta,
葛蘭納托·尼妲齊達
the strongest catfolk princess this generation has ever seen.
這一代最強的貓人族公主
Can I really defeat her?
我真的能夠贏過她嗎
Given your skill in swordplay,
憑你的劍術
you won't stand a chance even after ten thousand matches.
就算打一萬場也贏不了吧
So what's the point of this training?
那我特訓有什麼意義
I mean, I did somewhat notice it.
雖然我也隱約察覺到了
Don't forget the rings you're wearing.
你忘了戴在左手的東西嗎
Are you sure?
這樣好嗎
Using magic seems like cheating.
用魔法也太卑鄙了
Magic is the mage's muscles in combat.
魔力就像是魔法師的肌肉
It's considered a strength too, sir.
那也算是實力的一種喔 老爺
Plenty of human mages come for the blind date as well.
人類的魔法師也常常來參加相親
Well, they all got beaten up pretty badly.
不過大家都被狠狠打倒了
The rings' magic is extremely powerful.
戒指的魔法強度不同凡響
You just might win if you make use of it.
只要好好利用就有勝算
Probably.
應該吧
Come on, eat up.
好了 多吃點吧
You can't get stronger on an empty stomach.
不吃東西是無法變強的
Yeah!
好
Another challenger...
今天也有相親嗎
Incredible!
好厲害
Satou.
佐藤
Hime, it's you.
是小姬啊
You had a long day.
辛苦你了
Is the training over for today?
今天的特訓結束了嗎
No. I'm just taking a break.
還沒 只是休息一下
Gramps is giving me a magic lesson this afternoon.
爺爺說下午要教我魔法
I see.
是嗎
Can you lie down for a little?
你稍微躺一下
This is your reward for your hard work.
這是你努力的獎勵
What a gorgeous view.
景色真美好
Do you feel better now?
打起精神了嗎
Not just better.
何止有精神
With your encouragement,
要是能得到妳的鼓勵
I can take on any challenges.
不管多辛苦我都會努力
You're so innocent.
你真單純呢
So,
那個啊
it's okay for you to be weak, Satou.
就算你很弱也沒關係
But I can't be weak.
那樣不行吧
You are going to marry five princesses and collect their rings.
你只要跟五位公主結婚 收集到所有戒指
Then, you use the rings' power to fight. That's all.
然後好好發揮戒指的力量就夠了
The ring's power depends on our bond as husband and wife.
戒指的力量是看夫妻的情誼
I'll be sure to fulfil my duty.
這部分我會好好努力
You don't have to force yourself to become stronger.
你不需要勉強自己變強
But that would make me so useless.
可是這樣我不是超遜的嗎
Just maintain your slightly useless look.
你只要保持有點遜的模樣就好
That's it.
這樣就好
Satou, it's time for your magic training.
佐藤 差不多該進行魔法特訓了
I must go now.
我走了
I didn't understand a word Gramps said.
爺爺說的話我完全聽不懂
Am I going too hard?
力道還可以嗎
Satou.
佐藤
Ouch!
好痛
You did great today.
你今天真努力呢
You did pretty well for someone who has barely held a sword.
以剛拿劍沒多久的人來說 算是做得很好了
I was surprised
我覺得有點意外
by how good you are at martial arts.
沒想到你連武術都很擅長
Do I look that weak?
我看起來那麼瘦弱嗎
That's not what I mean...
不是啦 是因為…
I just don't take you for someone who likes fighting.
我看你好像不太喜歡爭鬥
Just a hunch.
只是感覺
As a member of the royal family,
身為皇族的人
I must be a scholar and a fighter.
必須文武雙全
That's just how it is with the kingdom I was born into.
我所在的帝國就是這樣的地方
My father and brother are even more impressive than me.
父親和兄長比我更了不起
I can't even hope to be as capable as them.
我根本無法與他們相比
But if you were the Ring King,
如果你是戒王
do you think you'd have a chance
你覺得自己有辦法
to defeat Granart Needakitta?
戰勝火之國公主葛蘭納托嗎
In terms of swordplay, I'd probably lose.
只論劍術 我應該也贏不過她
Is she that strong?
她有這麼強嗎
Gentlemen, would you like some scrubbing?
你們兩位要不要搓澡呢
It feels really nice.
很舒服喔
Could you scrub my back?
能麻煩幫我搓澡嗎
Scrub this gentleman's back.
請幫一位客人搓澡
I'm counting on you.
麻煩了
I'm scrubbing this gentleman's back.
幫一位客人搓澡
I should get going.
那我先走了
This can't be happening.
不會吧
Having smooth skin is the secret to becoming popular.
光滑的肌膚是受歡迎的祕訣
It also alleviates the fatigue you got from training.
還能消除鍛鍊的疲勞喔
Hold on!
等一下
Let's begin.
那我們開始吧
"SHINY" You look even more masculine now!
(充滿光澤) 變得很有男子氣概
The princess...
公主
Satou, right?
你叫佐藤吧
You may call me Granart.
叫我葛蘭納托就好
Well? Most of the fatigue should be gone now.
怎麼樣 疲勞應該消除了不少吧
Given the rare opportunity, I have a favour to ask.
機會難得 就拜託你吧
What...
呃 這是…
Scrub my back.
搓澡
You just had it. I'm pretty sure you can get it done.
你剛剛才做過 應該辦得到吧
But I'm a man
我是男的耶
and I know nothing about this!
而且還是門外漢
It doesn't matter.
無所謂
You lost in a fight against me.
你在相親的時候輸給我
It's not too much to do me a favour, no?
聽我一個要求應該無妨吧
Very well.
那好吧
How does my body feel?
我的肉體摸起來怎麼樣
It's... It's impressive.
好…好厲害
Underneath the smooth skin
光滑的肌膚底下
are the soft but rigorous muscles.
是柔軟結實的肌肉
Her arms are definitely
即使單純比腕力
stronger than mine.
我也一定贏不了她
I'm tired from the blind date today.
今天的相親也讓我好累
All the men who challenged me
來挑戰我的
were boring fellows too eager to prove their worth.
全都是只想著耀武揚威的無聊男人
Honestly, I'm sick of this.
老實說 我早就厭倦了
And then, you arrived.
這時候你出現了
It's the Ring Princess's duty to follow the Ring King.
追隨戒王是戒指公主的職責
I'd be glad to give you a hand.
我也很樂意助你一臂之力
I don't mind if you want me
我的意思是下次的相親
to throw the rematch.
要我輸給你也行
What...
什…
Shush.
噓
Not so loud.
你太大聲了
However, we must put on an act.
但是我們要做給別人看
It has to be convincing.
所以必須演得逼真一點
Just as you did to the other princesses,
就像你對其他公主做的那樣
simply make me yours.
把我占為己有就行了
This body
那副身體
will give you a great amount of pleasure.
應該能帶給你不少樂趣
I know those rings are the real deal.
我知道你手上的戒指不是裝飾品
At least you are worthy of wearing them.
你至少應該有戴上它們的資格
I'll cooperate from here on.
剩下的我會好好配合你
I don't need your pity.
不需要妳手下留情
I'll fight you with all I have!
我會拿出全力跟妳比賽
In that case, do your best.
那你就好好努力吧
I told Hime I wanted to become stronger.
還說什麼我一定要變強
This is humiliating.
簡直遜斃了